Le Nhat Quang

Summary

I'm a Front-end Software Engineer with 1-year of experience in Website Development. With my knowledge of UI/ UX design, I enjoy solving front-end problems and creating the best user experience for users.

Furthermore, I'm also an English teacher with a great passion for committing to provide the best learning experience for my students, and I am eager to contribute my expertise in improving the curriculum to fit the needs of each individual student.

Skills

- Programming Languages: JavaScript | TypeScript | C++ | C | MongoDB | Node | Express | React | Git
- Frameworks/ Platforms: ReactJS | AngularJS | Bootstrap | TailwindCSS | NodeJS | ExpressJS
- Frontend | Backend | Full-Stack | English (C1), Japanese (N5)

Experience _

YouTuber YouTube 03/2020 - Current

A YouTube channel that aims to share about my daily life, personal/ team project, and technology.

English Teacher Hallo English Ha Noi, Viet Nam 04/2023 - Current

- Planning and delivering effective English language lessons: Designing and implementing well-structured lesson plans that cater to the needs and abilities of diverse student populations, fostering language development, critical thinking, and creativity.
- Assessing and evaluating student progress and creating a positive and inclusive learning environment.
- Implementing effective classroom management strategies: Establishing and enforcing classroom rules and expectations, maintaining a safe and orderly learning environment, and resolving conflicts or behavioral issues with professionalism and fairness.

Editorial Manager YBOX Ha Noi, Viet Nam 12/2022 - 03/2023

- A social platform for youngsters which have an average of 1 million users per month.
- Edit and prove the posts on Ybox social page in many aspects.
- Manage the content of the general post.

English Teaching Assistant

VUS

Da Nang, Viet Nam

10/2022 - 02/2023

- Actively assist teachers in classroom management and class activities.
- Provide tutoring sessions for students and keep in touch with student's parents or guardians about their studying.

Science Research

Critical Thinking-Thinking for Success

Da Nang, Viet Nam

06/2021 - 12/2021

- Collaborated complication of curricula for the Critical Thinking Skill of Da Nang Highschool students.
- Organized the exercises that help students enhance their Critical Thinking Skills through a Social Fanpage.
- The achievement of the project is the second prize at Da Nang Science and Engineering Fair and <u>a Science Research Article</u> that was published in RA Journal Of Applied Research.

Education

Bachelor of Software Engineering

FPT University

Da Nang, Viet Nam

Studying

• Major in Electrical and Computer Engineering

Projects _

- CODEWITHME: An E-learning platform that helps students to learn to program by Pet Project. Link to <u>Github</u> (12/2023)
- CREATIVEWIDGET: Develop with the purpose to help customers create a website with a template. Website (1/2023 Current)

Others

- Impression Award: Won the impression prize for the FPT NihongoEng competition with the topic of "Beyond the Boundary". (03/2023)
- Second Prize at Da Nang Science and Engineering Fair provincial merit competition. (12/2021).
- I am keen on reading books, IT blogs, learning new technology, and teaching English to everyone. I am also really into writing and have had several prizes at Writing Competitions.